MAKSYM TSYBULSKYI

Sacramento, CA 95842 · 916-578-86-78 tomahawksmail@gmail · LinkedIn Profile · GitHub · WebSite

SUMMARY

I am an engineer with over 15 years of experience in IT. In total more than 12 years held the position of head of the IT department. My main qualities are self-management, responsibility and time-management. I always try to work for the result. I have completed a DevOps engineering course and I want to find a new job. I am always happy to learn something new and share my knowledge among my colleagues.

- Linux: Ubuntu, Debian, Amazon Linux

- MS Windows Server: AD, DNS, GPO, SMB

- Networking: Subnetting, TCP, UDP, HTTP(S), VPN

- laaC: Terraform

SQL: MySQL (MariaDB), MS SQL Server

Scripts: Python3, BashVersion Control: Git, GitHub

- Containers: Docker, Docker Compose, Swarm

- Clouds: AWS, Vodafone

- CI/CD: Jenkins, GitHub

Web server: NGINXOrchestration: Kubernetes

- Observability: Logging with ELK Stack

- WSGI: Gunicorn+Flask

- Synchronization: Rsync

- Virtualization: VMware, VMWare, Vagrant, ProxMox

- Configuration/Automation: Ansible

EXPERIENCE

07/2023 – CURRENT TIME SENIOR SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

USKO INC · FULL-TIME USA, RANCHO CORDOVA

- Maintenance, management and updating current IT Infrastructure
- Transfer all internal microservices to Docker Swarm
- Created Web App as a single entry point for monitoring and maintenance
- Preparing IT infrastructure for launching furniture production

02/2023 - 07/2023

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST

MAGMA LINE INC \cdot FULL-TIME

USA, SACRAMENTO

- Maintenance, management and adaptation e-commerce website
- Maintenance IT infrastructure
- Maintenance WEB server

12/2012 - 03/2022

HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT/ ARCHITECT

CLINIC OF SAINT CATHERINE · FULL-TIME

UKRAINE, ODESA

- Created the entire infrastructure of the company (purchase and configuration of equipment)
- Prepared and partial transfer of services to the Cloud (AWS and Vodafone)
- Automation and optimization of processes using Python
- Maintened and backup of multiple databases (MySQL and MS SQL Server)
- Maintain Kubernetes Clusters with own internal web services

- Construction and maintenance of IT infrastructure of the enterprise

05/2010 - 10/2012

HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT

"VIRTUS" · FULL-TIME UKRAINE, ODESA

01/2006 - 06/2010

CHIEF ENGINEER

SECURITY SYSTEMS INTEGRATOR

"AGENT-SB" · FULL-TIME

UKRAINE, ODESA

- Design and installation of security systems

- Created two websites for the company

- Maintened and backup of multiple databases

- Created the entire infrastructure of the company

EDUCATION

2000 - 2006

Evaluated in US Bachelor's Degree in Telecommunications,

ODESSA NATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS Information Communication Networks

UKRAINE, ODESA

COURSES & CERTIFICATES

ACADEMY BY O.S.POPOV

02/2022 HILLEL IT school DevOps

01/2023 AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

01/2022 TP-LINK CERTIFIED PARTNER 01/2023 Troubleshooting: Amazon API Gateway

07/2022 AWS Compute Services Overview

01/2023 AWS Networking Basics 12/2021 AWS TECHNICAL ESSENTIALS 01/2023 AWS Networking Basics

01/2023 AWS Network Monitoring and Troubleshooting